# **Adam Hoff**

(571) 439-9011 | adamhoff79@gmail.com | 16667 Goldencrest Circle, Purcellville VA 20132

## **Profile**

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

A 20 year old junior full-stack web developer with a passion for all things technology, I am able to work calmly and productively and finish the task at hand while under high stress and pressure. I am a quick learner, grasping new skills and ideas without hesitation and I am able to implement these skills throughout my work. My optimism and curiosity for web development will only keep growing as I continue to use innovating technologies to create stunning front-end designs and formulate clever solutions to back-end obstacles.

# Experience

### LIFEGUARD, FRANKLIN PARK POOL

MAY 2012-SEP 2016

Red Cross CPR and First Aid trained and certified. Helped teach new employees how to handle emergency situations at our facility; ensured compliance with established rules and guidelines by both employees and patrons; helped maintain constant surveillance of patrons within the facility; assisted with pool maintenance. Through the performance of numerous rescues while on duty, I learned how to perform well under stress and pressure. When needed, I acted immediately and appropriately to secure safety of patron sin the event of an emergency, providing emergency care and treatment as required until the arrival of emergency medical services

### LIFEGUARD, STONELEIGH GOLF & COUNTRY CLUB

**MAY 2014-AUG 2015** 

Red Cross CPR and First Aid trained and certified. helped maintain constant surveillance of patrons within the facility; ensured compliance with established rules and guidelines by patrons; assisted with pool maintenance.

# Education

University of Mary Washington, Fredericksburg VA	2014-2016
General Assembly; Web Development Immersive, Washington D.C.	Mar 2017-June 2017

# Areas of Expertise

Front-end	development	Agile programming	Τ	Object oriented programming
Front-end	design	Git workflows	I	Team collaborating
Technical Ski	lls			
HTML	CSS	JavaScript		jQuery
React	Ruby on Rails	S AngularJS		PostgressQL
Projects				

## http://adamhoff.github.io/portfolio

Front-end portfolio containing my projects and other information about myself.